{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "___ had we got into the building than it began to rain.",
      "a": "No sooner",
      "b": "The moment",
      "c": "Hardly",
      "d": "Directly",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- No sooner + had + S + p.p + than \n- Hardly + had + S + p.p + when \n- The moment (that) + S + ... \n- Directly (when) + S +...",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "6",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Let a man be ___ so rich, he should not live an idle life.",
      "a": "however",
      "b": "ever",
      "c": "no matter",
      "d": "whatever",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- Ever so = very",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "6",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Should a world war break out, no country would be able to ___ a crushing blow.",
      "a": "shut itself off from",
      "b": "shut off itself to",
      "c": "shut itself off upon",
      "d": "shut on itself against",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- shut + oneself + off from",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "6",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Maurice could not so ___ as write his own name.",
      "a": "little",
      "b": "few",
      "c": "much",
      "d": "more",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- Not so much as ...",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "6",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "We can no _________ live without sleep than without food.",
      "a": "little",
      "b": "much",
      "c": "most",
      "d": "more",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- No more ... than",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "6",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "How often did you give her money? \" ___ than I can remember\"",
      "a": "More time",
      "b": "More times",
      "c": "The more time",
      "d": "The more times",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- How often .... more times ... ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "6",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "The poor old man was so ill that he died ___ last month.",
      "a": "sometime",
      "b": "sometimes",
      "c": "some times",
      "d": "some time",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- sometime: at a time in the future or in the past, although you do not know exactly when.\n- sometimes: on some occasions but not always",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "6",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Are you going so soon? Won't you stay with us ___ longer?",
      "a": "a little",
      "b": "little",
      "c": "just",
      "d": "a just",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- A little longer",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "6",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "What time is it now? \"It is five o'clock ___\"",
      "a": "just",
      "b": "yet",
      "c": "sharp",
      "d": "on time",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- Five o'clock sharp: at exactly 5:00",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "6",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is ___ cold here in this classroom.",
      "a": "much and",
      "b": "very nice",
      "c": "more and",
      "d": "nice and",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- Nice and cold: used with another adjective to emphasize that you like a particular quality that someone or something else.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "6",
      "subcategorylv2": "5",
      "type": "5"
    }
  ]
}